Jim & Andy: The Great Beyond is a documentary, drama,
comedy film directed by Chris Smith.
Offbeat documentarian Chris Smith provides a behind-the-scenes look at how Jim Carrey adopted
the persona of idiosyncratic comedian Andy Kaufman on the set of Man on the Moon.
Self, played by Jim Carrey.
Self, played by Danny DeVito.
Self, played by Miloš Forman.
Self, played by Judd Hirsch.
Self, played by Peter Bonerz.
Self, played by Randall Carver.
Jim & Andy: The Great Beyond – Featuring a Very Special, Contractually Obligated Mention of Tony Clifton (or
simply Jim & Andy: The Great Beyond) is a 2017 American documentary film directed by Chris Smith.
The film follows actor Jim Carrey as he remains in character as Andy Kaufman during the
production of the 1999 film Man on the Moon, directed by Miloš Forman.
It was released on November 17, 2017, through the streaming service Netflix.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.